# Jon Nielsen

jon-nielsen@hotmail.com | 251952459632 | Bole Rwanda, Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Region, Ethiopia | https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonnielsen1/ | 1988-06-18

## **Profile Summary**

I am a versatile economist striving to use economic analysis to the benefit of the least advantaged. I have extensive experience in doing macroeconomic model calculations, data analyses and literature reviews, and in presenting my findings in a non-technical way. Further, I have experience as team leader, coordinator and project manager.

### **Work Experience**

Head of Section at Ministry of Finance of Denmark (2015-08-25 - 2017-06-07)

Location: Copenhagen, Denmark

Chief Analyst at Economic Council of The Labour Movement (2017-06-08 - 2024-05-31)

Location: Copenhagen, Denmark Responsibilities: Economic analyses

#### **Education**

#### **Master's Degree in Economics**

Institution: University of Cambridge | Dates: 2014-08-31 - 2017-06-07

Location: Cambridge, United Kingdom

#### **Skills & Tools**

#### Languages

**English**